# **Alejandro Krasovsky**

### **Software Engineer**

alejandrok93@gmail.com (619) 564 - 1131 San Diego, CA <u>linkedin.com/alejandrokrasovsky</u> <u>github.com/alejandrok93</u> <u>alejandrok.me</u>

Product-focused developer with 2+ years of experience delivering software applications in an agile environment. Skilled at collaborating with an interdisciplinary team of developers, designers, and product managers to launch user-centered software applications.

#### **Technical Skills:**

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Node.js

Web APIs

SQL

React.is

Redux

Git

## **Projects**

**Qraft** · Team of 5 · November 2018 - December 2018

Qraft is a web application to publish interesting DIY projects and review projects uploaded by other users

- Utilized ReactJS and Redux on the frontend to build a responsive web application for viewing, creating, and reviewing DIY projects
- Developed web APIs with NodeJS and Express that connected with a PostgreSQL database to retrieve data
- Used Auth0 for authentication and AWS S3 for image storage

**GitHub Link:** github.com/Lambda-School-Labs/Labs8-RateMyDIY

Website Link: Qrafts.app

**Micro** · Team of 4 · October 2018 - December 2018

Micro is a marketplace for governments to make fully-compliant micro-purchases offered by the company Social Glass

- Developed the user interface with HTML and CSS to build a fully responsive website that matches the UX specifications
- Collaborated with a global team to build the marketplace in an agile environment

Website Link: <a href="mailto:themicro.market">themicro.market</a>

## **Experience**

### **PriceWaterhouseCoopers** · San Francisco, CA · June 2015 – July 2018

#### **EXPERIENCED ASSOCIATE** (AUG 2016 – JULY 2018)

- Spearheaded development and delivery of 5 mobile app projects, including Digital Membership Card, Find a Doctor, Precision Analytics, UX redesign, and Find Care to be functional on iOS and Android OS for over 6 million users
- Managed a 12-person engineering and QA team, ensuring delivery of new, innovative features for consumer-facing mobile application of a major healthcare provider
- Collaborated with engineering teams, effectively communicating to ensure clarity of project vision and full understanding of overall product requirements
- Drove all scrum meetings with engineering team and stakeholders, ensuring successful delivery of sprint commitments

#### **TECHNOLOGY CONSULTANT INTERN** (JUNE 2015 – AUG 2015)

 Designed and developed a working prototype of a mobile application built to identify heart irregularities from a wearable device

### **Education**